Thank you for watching.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen, the morning chimes have arrived, and it's us, the series MCs.
Before we begin, we'd like to choose today's MC for the series.
Please cast your votes for your choice between 1 and 2, and the MC will be the one who has that number written on his or her face.
So let's start the voting.
Which one is it?
I really want Yuno-chan to be the MC!
Yuno, you're a survey orc every time.
I'm not a survey orc.
Every time Yuno MC is chosen for this.
I want Emma to do it.
Come here.
You can see she's only wearing nail polish on one hand.
Excuse me.
Close. Five, four, three, two, one.
Okay. What do we have?
Oh, number one is 150.7 and number two is 49.3.
Oh, yeah, the raw sound is so loud!
The technique with the highest number is today's mc.
Okay, I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, with love... yes, I'll do mc.
I'll be doing mc, attendance number 14, also from Kokubun. I'll do my best.
Yes, please, to Sakura, attendance number 16.
Yes...
I can't turn my hair back now.
Let's start the showroom!
Thank you very much for visiting the 56th Shrimps' Delightful and Hilarious Showroom.
Thank you very much for watching our showroom, the 56th edition of Shrimp in the Shrimp Club's Delightful and Hilarious Showroom, the sister showroom of our sister showroom, Uka's Showroom.
So, if you would like to have an original avatar of Ebichu's showroom, please register with our showroom and pay for a free avatar.
You can get one by registering in our showroom and giving us a free or paid gift!
It's a bit crowded with all kinds of characters, so please make everyone an original avatar of Shrimp Shabichu!
I always forget what this is. I always forget what it's called.
I don't know what's the difference between this one and the mediocre one.
What's this one called?
Shrimp Heibonjin.
I don't know. I don't know. I hope Kaho won't notice. Please help us spread the word on Twitter by clicking on the Twitter icon at the bottom of the screen.
So here is the time to spread the word. I'm going to tweet an announcement on Twitter now so that as many people as possible can see it, so please retweet it.
What are you going to do? Pose.
What would you like?
Anything is fine. You decide.
I don't like this one.
Then let's do this.
I've been betrayed.
Please retweet these guys for a second. Please do.
Okay, today I would like to do a project like this. I'd like to do this project today.
Before we do a talk, we take a questionnaire and decide what we are going to talk about in a questionnaire talk.
Well then, I think it's time to show you the questionnaire talk.
Let's see.... There are so many things to talk about.
Please vote for your favorite talk and we will talk about the one that comes out on top.
I will talk a lot about the one that comes out on top.
Okay, then, let's start voting! Then, let the voting begin!
Today, Yuno bought some nail polish,
I asked Ema to try on one hand.
Just one hand.
I tried it on one hand,
I didn't have time to do it, so I hid it.
I hid it.
That's right.
The first is the Blu-ray release of Hinata Kashiwagi's Graduation Ceremony & University Alumni Association.
It was released on March 29.
The second is the final of Musha Shugyou free live.
The third is the Spring Tour coming soon.
Setouchi Idol Festival.
New solo Asha.
Simple Significance to the Japanese language is sparkle sparkle sparkle.
Lip.
Yunayama talk.
Then I'll close the voting.
Three, two, one.
What is it?
I wonder.
Bishop Musashi wants to hear it.
Number one is number two.
No. 2 means Bishop Musashi's free live concert final.
Yes, that's right.
Last April 1 was the final day of Bishop Musashi's Free Live, wasn't it?
Yes, in Osaka.
In Osaka.
Yes.
At JACO ATC.
How was it?
I don't know. I don't know, it was the final,
I don't know.
I was even more nervous.
I don't know. I felt like I had grown up,
I felt like I had grown. Finally, on the fifth time.
But I was surprised at how open it was.
Nanko ATC Umebe stage?
We did it near the ocean.
I wonder if any of you commented on it.
They said it was really great.
Thank you very much.
Up until now, we've always had unidentified junior high school students and Voyager as a fixture at every show,
This time, we eliminated all of the fixed songs,
I was so excited to see the family members' war when we played "Made in Japan" one day.
We were all talking about how we wanted to do that song for sure.
We all put it in, and yes, we did.
How did you feel about the jump for the final score break?
Were you surprised?
Either the jump or the seven colors,
We decided to include one song from each of our various albums, such as Ebikurashii for this Musha Shugyo free live performance,
We decided to include a song from each of our various albums,
We needed to tell the stories of the sister members alone, but also to tell the stories of the five of us, or episodes of our lives,
How did you feel about including all of them?
How was it?
The five of us got to know each other really well,
I'm really glad we did it.
Yes, it was.
We talked about doing either Jump or Nanairo, right?
Yes, the five of us talked about it and decided which one we would do.
But I hope we can do both someday.
The jump was really good. I was very impressed.
Thank you very much.
You didn't fight?
We didn't fight.
We had a scoring meeting.
Is it true that Rika came up with the idea?
It is true, isn't it?
That's right.
We really had a lot of new members,
I was on my way home from the showroom right after MN was announced,
I was just talking to the manager about the idea of doing a live concert with the five of us.
I didn't know that.
It was great because I had said I wanted to do it with the five of us,
I am very happy.
Did you eat anything in Osaka?
Osaka?
Oh, I had negiyaki.
It was really delicious.
I had the cheese cake with leeks,
How about you and Yuna?
Yuna had kushikatsu.
We go to Osaka every time we go there.
It was really delicious.
Shall we move on to the next topic?
Yes, we are.
Okay, let's start the voting. Please vote.
Please do.
Are we voting now?
Which ones are you guys interested in?
There's just so much going on.
We're right in the middle of rehearsals for the spring tour,
It's right after it was released,
It was just the other day, just the other day, just the other day,
It's just the other day, just the other day, just the other day.
So this is pretty good, too.
What do you think?What do you think?
Closing in three, two, one.
How's it going? What's going on?
Six!
Well, Happy Birthday, Kokubue.
Happy birthday. Kokubue-no-san.
Yes, that's right. Sorry.
We had a birthday party for you on your birthday,
How was it? You came to see it, right? Now.
I went to see it,
What? What was it?
It was THE!
What do you mean?
It was really a live concert where Yuna-chan's mamma was on display,
Of course, the live performance was the same,
The live performance of course, but the MCs in between were also very Yuna-chan,
As you can see, Yuna-chan was very fast-paced,
It was a lot of fun to watch.
I loved the banter.
What is that?
I liked the emotion train.
I'm glad.
I was thinking of doing "Emotion Train" and "Please Jesus,
I was thinking of doing "Emotion Train" and "Please Jesus," both of which were not sung when we were nine.
I was going to make a block of songs that were never sung,
But I felt sorry for the staff, so I decided not to do it.
The costumes were so cute.
It was cute.
I found the costume designer by myself on Instagram,
I asked her to do it for me.
It was some kind of headdress.
The headdress was really cute.
Yuna Kuroko's live show was packed with cute parts.
I'm glad.
I was betrayed by the fact that they didn't play many of the songs I had prepped.
I wondered what I had prepared for.
But there were a lot of songs that Yuna would have chosen.
That's for sure.
It was really emo that she sang the song she sang during the audition.
I guess she's the Yuna Kuroko.
The Kuroko Yuna.
She really is the Yuna Kuroko.
Did any of you see it on the site?
Certainly, there were a lot of people who watched the streaming.
Thankfully, everyone bought tickets.
Emma said, "Emma, you're so nice to me.
Do you have any advice for Emma?
Yes, I do. If Yuna is born, that means Emma is born too, right?
Well, I don't know.
Ebichu's songs are difficult.
There are a lot of songs that are not suitable to sing alone.
That's for sure. But there are a lot of times when they are sung by the same person, right?
Because we sing in groups,
I can catch my breath because the parts are divided,
But when I sing alone, I can't catch my breath.
That's true. It is difficult.
I can understand that. It's definitely difficult for everyone to sing karaoke, isn't it?
That's true.
But he also said he watched the video. Thank you very much.
Hey.
You should decide on your back training early.
I see.
You should think about it soon.
Really. You should think about it sooner rather than later.
Next, Anky.
Me?
I'm the only one who can do it.
Congratulations.
Fifth grade.
I see that we both lost our junior high school students on April 1. Only high school students.
I thought it was kind of nice that all the younger members are high school students.
I thought it would be nice to wear uniforms to Disney or something.
And now Cocona is giving up, so we are just in time.
I have to go soon.
I have to go.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Kon-san, let's say 16 things we like about Yuno.
We did this with Maya, didn't we?
Yes, we did. Yuno and the others said 26.
Sixteen. And all by yourself.
Yeah. Do your best.
It's not something to work hard for.
Go at your own pace.
You have beautiful hands.
Nice style.
Thank you.
Gummies.
Mental care.
I don't know what that means.
Your face is so tiny.
There are 10 more.
The part where he gets involved with me in weird ways.
And the part where he turns into a koala.
Koala.
The part where he turns into a sushi.
That's not my favorite part. Definitely not.
Your nails are always so cute.
Thank you.
Six more.
Don't worry about it.
There are, but there are so many, I'm having a bit of trouble.
There are six more things to do.
The part where you tell me all kinds of trivia.
I see.
And then..,
There were gummy bears, weren't there?
Yes, there were.
I don't know, I'm looking at them. I'm looking at them.
I'm looking at his face.
I admire the way he writes a blog and posts on TikTok every day.
Thank you. And the other three...
And three more things... the cute birthday outfit, the cute birthday outfit... and...
And...
And the way you always calm me down when I'm in a hurry at lessons and stuff,
Mental?
And the other thing is..,
The ring is cute.
Your ring is cute. Thank you.
I always had it.
And..,
This one.
It's cute.
What else do we have?
How many more?
The rest is done.
It's done.
Yay!
I knew Mayama-san's 26 was great.
That was amazing.
I did my best. I did my best.
What made you happiest?
What made me happiest was your beautiful fingers.
I think your fingers are really beautiful.
Yes, they are.
They are long.
I used to have really deep nails,
They are healing little by little, and now they are much better, so I am very happy.
I have an image of you putting a lot of effort into your hands.
Because I had deep nails.
I put a lot of effort into healing them.
Shall we go to the next survey?
I'm ready for it now.
Start!
I want to heal my deep nails too.
I started gel nails and they healed instantly.
Please do gel nails.
Gel nails and just apply nail oil all over.
That's how I healed little by little.
Surprisingly, 7 and 8 are not so much with anyone ...Surprisingly, 7 and 8 are not so much with anyone ...
This is a story that doesn't seem to be in much demand.
It's a little bit dense at the top.
What do you think?
I'll close it.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Close.
What is it?
Eight.
Which one of you wrote 8?
I just wrote it.
Lately, I've been taking lessons for the spring tour, so I didn't have any great episodes to tell you about,
So I decided to make it a Yunoyama episode,
First of all, there is the sushi and the koala that I mentioned earlier,
Recently, I was having a lesson,
I had to wait and take a break,
There are 10 of us.
That's right.
Everyone is pretty tired.
So Ema was lying on the bed like this, with her head in her hands.
Then Uno-chan came on top of her with all her might,
She said, "Sushi.
What? Coconut probably took a picture of it, so I'll definitely put it in the story today,
I'll definitely put it in the story today.
I told her that it was Yunoyama's specialty,
And then there is the koala.
The koala is just an imitation of Yunoyama-chan following him around,
I'll show you the sushi later.
I'll put some sushi on the table later.
And Yunoyama-chan's hoodie is yellowish green,
It looks like wasabi, and it's very sushi-like.
Speaking of koalas, Yuna and I were watching a scary movie together the other night.
It was on the day of the student idol festival in Hiroshima.
There was a scene that surprised me a little,
Yuna said, "Excuse me,
Yuna said, "Excuse me for a minute.
She was scared.
Do you get it when Yuna comes suddenly and says, "Excuse me, I'm sorry.
Yuna-chan is always so abrupt, so be careful.
There's nothing you can do if you don't see it.
Yun-chan is always sudden, so be careful.
I'm sorry.
Is Kawachii here?
It's "kawachii. If he does it suddenly.
I'm just in the middle of a lesson for the spring tour.
Tickets for the spring tour are still available at some venues,
Please buy them. I'd be happy if you could come.
That's great.
Shall we go on to the next survey?
Yes.
Okay. I think we have about two more to go? Yes. Please do. Start!
I'm going to Aichi! Ah! I'm so happy. What will you sing?
You sing "Inu no omawarisan" or something, right? I was told I would sing "Elephant". I don't know yet. We don't know each other's set. Yes, that's right.
Are you anti-German?
Oh, no.
Is it a solo version?
Yes, it is. Solo version.
Okay, let's close the survey.
Five, four, three, two, one.
What?
Spring tour coming up.
That's right.
As I told you earlier,
April 15?
Tickets are now on sale for the Spring Tour, which will start on April 15.
How do you like it?
How are you doing? I'm in the middle of a lesson. This is my first spring tour.
It's a lot of work.
That's right. It's a spring tour.
I'm giving lessons to 10 people right now,
I don't know. But this time..,
Is it cool?
I think it's an interesting story.
I think it's a great story, and I think it can be enjoyed by fans from any period of time.
I'm sure there will be a lot of "ohhhh" moments.
Be careful of spoilers.
I won't.
Are you sure you won't? I'm most worried.
What?
I don't want to be told by ℃-ute.
What kind of choreography will you use for the new song?
I'll have to wait and see if we do or don't do a new song.
Indeed.
I wonder. Which part are you looking forward to the most?
The beginning, the middle, or the very end?
I wonder.
But I think I like the first part a lot.
For sure.
Not the beginning, but the end of the middle.
Oh, that part is fun.
Pay attention to this one.
I want them to come.
I really want you to come. I really want you to come.
You can even speak out,
There are various regulations depending on the venue,
There may be some venues that don't allow it,
But please come.
I would really like to have a lot of fun with you.
See you,
Let's announce the spring tour now.
Yes, I'm going on a spring tour.
I'm going for the first time in four years. I'm psyched. Thank you very much.
We will participate in a lot of events. Please come to all of them.
℃-ute Ebisu Chugaku Spring Tour 2023 100% Ebizum will start on April 15,
Please come and see us.
There are still some tickets left,
Tokyo, Kanto, or Ibaraki?
Yes, I think so. Cocona is going to be a bit pouty,
Please come,
Please come to Aichi on May 5th.
Which venue? There are some prefectures you haven't been to yet.
Yes, there are. There are a lot of them.
Where are you looking forward to eating?
Hokkaido.
You've never been to Hokkaido?
I'm really looking forward to Hokkaido.
There is a Hokkaido, isn't there?
Yes, there is.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm going to Hokkaido. Thank you very much.
Do you have any recommendations for souvenirs from Hokkaido?
I'd love to hear.
Hokkaido people who are watching this.
Hokkaido residents?
That's right, May 5th is the 2nd anniversary of your joining us here in Hokkaido.
That's great.
We have seafood, too.
Shiroi Koibito.
Last year, during the spring tour, we got a can of Shiroi Koibito with the Ebichu spring tour logo on it,
He made it for me,
I still have it at home.
It's so cute.
Jagapokkuru.
What is jagapokkle?
It's like dried potato McDonald's fries.
Wow.
It feels dry.
Amazing.
Like a snack.
You ate a lot of Yuno-chan, didn't you?
Yes, I have. Hokkaido is delicious.
It's delicious.
Why is May 5 a day to get angry?
Yes, May 5th is a day when everyone should be careful.
It's a day to be careful and do your best.
Oh, I see.
Let's do our best.Let's do our best.
We can't let our guard down. All the performances, though.
Lloyds Chocolate Potatoes.
Looks delicious.
I want some. I'm hungry now.
Well, it's time for one more.
Is this the last one? It's about time.
I would like to go to the last survey, so you can vote twice for the same one,
Please vote.
Oh~
I don't like number 6 or something.
I'll have you go 16th once more for number 6.
Because May 5 is the anniversary of the major label's debut, plus the 2nd anniversary of Koino's joining.
That's great.
Hey... What's going to happen?
What's going to happen?
What does everyone want to see?
I don't know.
M.I.A. You've been with us for six months now, right?
Right.
Okay, I'll close the voting.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
The end.
What do you think?
1,900 people watched the show.
That's amazing. Thank you very much.
Number one is number 7.
Number 7.
This really happened on the day of the birthday party,
Ruri Uguka came to see me on my birthday and gave me a lipstick as a birthday present.
I thought I should tell you about this delightful and fluffy showroom, which is Ugka's little sister,
The lipstick I'm using today was also given to me by Ruri.
So cute.
Ruri-chan.
Next to the lip box with the cute lip packaging, I also got a box of gummy bears.
Gummies, indeed.
There was a dark cherry of fruit juice gummies next to the cute bag of gummies.
It's nice. Gummi Tomo.
Akita Bunko and others are having a gummy party together.
That's great.
I love it.
It's nice to have food friends.
If you ask them for a recommendation, they will definitely tell you, so you should definitely contact them.
What kind of gummi do you recommend, Yuna-chan?
Hino-chan recommended Kororo sugar brocade gummies, which were only available for a limited time,
Some places still sell them, so please try them.
I see.
I want to try them.
They are delicious.
I bought some peach gummies earlier today, too.
Hino-chan definitely has gummy bears,
If you want to eat gummy bears, please stay with Yuna-chan.
I won't give them to everyone. That's for members only.
That's for members only.
Don't go too far.
On the contrary,
It's not Emma's lipstick recommendation, but..,
But it's my favorite lip.
Hmmm...
But I like ROM&'s series a lot.
Heh...
I don't know anything about lips,
I guess I don't know that much.
I'm sure women can relate to it.
Hmmm... Indeed.
I told her that it's the best cosmetics.
What? The best?
The best, really.
Oh, Jill Stuart is good, too.
Oh, that's good? That one.
I got it from Ruri.
Hmmm.
Hmmm...
I don't know what it is.
Maybe it's a gift for your girlfriend.
If you give her a lipstick as a present, she'll be delighted.
What color lipstick do you want?
I want red lips.
I'd rather have a little red than pink.
It makes her say, "Oh, wow!
Oh!
It's hard to get a lipstick as a gift, isn't it? I'm sure everyone has a hard time with lipstick.
Oh, yeah.
That's true. You never know, do you?
I guess everyone looks for gifts like this.
This is how everyone is looking for it. Lips.
Yes, they do.
Yol lips are cute.
It is.
I may have never used them.
Yole was checked out by Coconut yesterday.
Eh~.
I thought it was as good as I expected.
Coconut likes that kind of thing.
That's great.
Well, I'd like to end the survey now.
Okay.
That's all for now.
Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle.
Coconut-san is amazing, isn't he?
You are indeed amazing.
Well then, today is the first distribution of the new year,
Oh~. Oh, I see.
Here is the project.
It's called, "A Joyful and Happy New Life.
No, no, no.
I'm sure many of you are starting a new life in April, living on your own, going to a new workplace or school, changing classes, and so on,
I think there are many people who are starting a new life.
So today, I'm going to give them a big push.
We are both still minors,
To all the questions and nags coming from you all,
I will answer them with the same hands that have been doing it for weeks of my life.
How can I get into your class? And,
How do I get along with my boss?
By all means, come talk to us about anything.
No, I've been doing this for weeks.
How many weeks?
I have,
I'm probably..,
About 121 weeks.
I'm a very old lady.
This is only the sixth time I've said that.
I still have a long way to go.
Today is the entrance ceremony,
I guess there are people like that.
Please tell me how to refuse a drinking party.
I've been doing this for 102 weeks.
Drinking? How do you turn down a drinking party?
Turn it down?
You know what I'm talking about. Of course.
Yes, I do.
I think..,
It's better to say that you have plans.
Simply from experience,
I think it's better to say that you can't do it because you have plans after that.
I think it's better to say that you have plans because it will make the other person feel better.
But there is always the possibility that they will find out that you lied.
So I think it's better to be very particular about what you say.
I don't want to go.
That's right.
If you lie too much, it will look like you are very busy.
That's true.
I think it would be better to say that you want to play games today and that you are going home.
Next question.
How do you ask a junior to dinner?
I'm also a pro at saying this.
What do you want to eat? and then ask her if she would like to go with you or if she would like to go somewhere she wants to go. Or, you can ask them if they want to go to a place you want to go now,What do you want to eat? and ask her if she would like to go with you or if she would like to go with you to the place you want to go. Then I would ask him if he wanted to go with me or to a place I wanted to go,
Then we go on that day.
This is something I get a lot of requests for.
YUNO often asks me to go with him, and we often go together.
You went to Aka Karaoke with MONJA, didn't you?
That's right. The five of us go together quite often.
On the other hand, you were already a senior in junior high school, right?
You are in the third grade of junior high school, so you had juniors in the first and second grades, right?
You had dinner with juniors?
Or with juniors in your club?
How do you ask them out?
But..,
You've done 20 rounds of 100 yen.
That's right.
When you ask a junior member to go out with you, you should just go out of your way to be superior.
What's this?
I'm still a junior, and some of them may have done 6 rounds like this,
I'd say, "Hey, how about dinner today? I think it's a good idea to ask them out,
I think you should ask them out.
Do you mean I should go for the "ora ora" type of attitude?
Don't put pressure on them,
If you put pressure on them, you will never be able to do it again, so don't put pressure on them.
I see.
What should I do in my third year as a working adult?
Working people? I've kind of forgotten.
I've forgotten.
What did you do in your previous life?
Previous life?
In the 119th lap.
What will you do in your third year of work?
I guess I'm going to cut my hair.
I see.
Why?
Because it is important to look clean,
In your third year, you are getting used to it,
So I cut my hair a little bit,
I changed my look a little bit,
I think it's important to do that,
I think it is important to do so.
I recommend getting a haircut.
Is there any recommendation?
I'm in my third year,
I'm no longer a first-year rookie,
I may have gone from being just a junior to a senior,
I may have gone from being a junior to a senior, and I may have gone from being a junior to a senior,
So I would like to have dinner with the second generation.
I will go out to dinner with them again.
So you have two juniors.
For two years.
Dinner is important.
You have to get to know them a little better over dinner.
What do I have to do to get ahead?
Isn't that Emma?
How do I get ahead?
Advancement?
What do you mean, promotion?
You know what I'm talking about. Career advancement.
I know,
I've trained a hundred people.
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it,
I knew it,
To own a restaurant.
Out of the blue.
Because that's what it's all about.
I've had success in my career, too,
It's hard work to get ahead, after all.
But, I think it's great to own a store.
I can do what I want,
I can do what I want to do, and I can do what I want to do,
I think it is a good idea to work hard and own your own store in order to get ahead.
I am now a new member of society.
I want to be a boss and become a section manager. I don't want to be a manager,
I am now a working adult.
I will own my own store.
That is the fastest way.
That's true.
I see.
That's great.
Eh? Yuno-san, how do you get ahead?
The way to get ahead is to give gummy bears to everyone.
You have to make gummy bears.
You give them gummy bears, and they remember you as the person who gave them to them the other day.
Oh, wow. Wow, that's great.
I've done it six times.
The last time was when I was an office worker.
I see.
Then, let's see what's next.
Tell us how to win the college entrance exam.
College entrance exam? How to win.
You also took the high school entrance exam, right?
Yes, I did.
I took it 100 times.
Twenty times.
I stopped 20 times.
I took the exam 100 times.
How do you win a college entrance exam?
I'm not sure if I'm going to pass or not.
I think I'm more enthusiastic if I wear a hachimaki (headband).
Does that mean anything?
It's a must-win.
I think my chances go up if I wear a hachimaki.
I've done it 100 times, so I tried it out. I've tried it a hundred times.
First of all, there are two ways,
I tried two ways of winding it up,
I tried winding it with the words "Hisho wa Bikkuri Waku" written on it,
I tried it,
It is better to roll it up.
I see.
If you wind it up, it will go up quite a bit.
You will pass.
I see.
You have to have guts.
Is that guts? No?
I don't know.
You have to pray to various gods.
Go to shrines all the time.
I actually used to use THE LIFE 10 MONTH mechanical pencil.
I was using a mechanical pencil to do it.
And don't believe in not studying with friends.
Oh, sure.
You do it behind the scenes.
What qualifications do you have that are useful at work?
Certifications?
How many certifications do you have?
Including past lives.
Qualifications?
About two?
Qualifications are probably not my strong point.
I see.
Qualifications?
One,
What was it again?
Kanji Certificate?
Kanji Proficiency Test,
And an English proficiency test.
That's all the skills I have.
That's why I have to work. But it's useful, isn't it?
Kanji and English.
If you don't have level 2 or above, you can't use it much.
What level did you pass?
Level 3.
Just barely.
I am also 3rd grade in English.
I can say I can speak English.
I can say "Hello," so I can talk to anyone.
Is this a useful qualification?
Right now, I am actually trying to get a certification in aromatherapy.
I am thinking of taking it.
I like bath salts.
It's something that will help me in my work.It is to be useful as my job.
As my job.
But I would say that I collect Yuna.
I am interested in aromatherapy and color psychology.
Color?
I like colors, so I'm a little curious.
Yes, that's right.
How about a driver's license?
Sounds good.
What do you have in mind? Other questions.
Please ask me questions.
I'll answer anything.
How do I become irresistible?
This is also irresistible, right?
Yes, I am.
What do I have to do to be popular?
I guess you just have to be sociable, right?
I don't know.
I think you should just keep smiling.
Is that bad? It's popular.
After that..,
What color clothes would have made you the most popular?
Clothes?
White.
White is the most popular color.
White is girly.
For a guy.
Gold?
If you wear gold, women will come to you. That era will come someday.
Eh?
Mr. Yuno.
How to be popular?
I realized for the sixth time.
I knew I had to ask her out to dinner.
I know a good restaurant there.
That's what she thinks.
Like Miru-chan, I'm a food logger.
It's better to be a source of superiority.
You certainly think you know about food, don't you?
That's what I think.
You should wear the gold one after all.
Matsuken-san, too.
Well, I guess I have a past life after all.
That's all for now.
It's difficult.
This is the end of the 56th edition of Ebichu's Delightful and Foofy Showroom.
Let's make an announcement.
Yes, I'm ready.
Okay.
You want to start from here?
Yes, yes, Silzebish Work's 14th single will be released today, on May 3!
We are also going to hold a free live concert at Seven Park Arioka Island Smile Park on April 16th.
How do you like it?
We'll have a two-shot event, and we'll be able to see each other for the first time in a long time, so please come and join us!
I'll be waiting for you.
One more thing.
Yasumoto Ayaka, Kobayashi Kacha, Nakamura Yuna's birthday solo live has been decided!
Yay! Check the official website for details!
It took Yuna 2 years after joining the group.
Yes, I'm so envious of you.
I've already announced this, but I'll do it again. The Private Ebisu Stuarts Ring Tour 2023100% Ebism will start on April 15th.
We'll be selling tickets at some venues, so please come and join us.
Okay, I'd like to see the top 5 of the final ranking.
What's up? It just flew in!
Happy birthday to you!
Thank you so much! May I open it?
Wow, wow, wow, Naima's Happy Birthday toe is so strong, I'm so surprised!
I wonder what it is... I'll open it.
A set of assorted gummies!
Thank you so much!
I love these gummies so much! It's nice to meet you!
I'm going to eat it and go home!
Thank you very much!
4th place, thank you Jimmy! 3rd place, thank you Monta!
That concludes the 56th edition of Emichu's Delightful and Funny Showroom. We will let you know about the next edition as soon as it is decided!
We'll let you know as soon as we have the next installment.
If there is anything you would like to tell us in the review session, please feel free to comment.
I was the star of the show.
See you later!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much for watching!
Yes, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The gummies have changed, haven't they?
Yes. Gong has changed a little bit.
It's moved a little bit.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
How was it, MC?
MC: Well, it was the first time for us to do it together,
How do we talk now?
I got to know how you speak now and how you speak as a professional.
But it says that you were a great MC.
I think it was the best MC I've ever done.
I'm so happy.
I can feel Yunopi's growth.
Yunopi's delivery is amazing without being uncomfortable.
I'm so happy. Thank you so much.
I can't see Kikko MC now.
Hinata-chan was pointing her finger at me and telling me what to do.
How was Ema?
It was really easy.
Working with Ema-chan.
Ema's assist was great.
Ema-chan's talk was also very interesting.
Thank you very much.
Ema Yuno.
I don't have any regrets.
The new life project was discussed at the meeting.
I asked you to do it without folding.
I'll do it without folding it.
For many weeks of my life.
I was asked to do it as if I was going to throw it away.
That was fun.
I'm glad. Thank you very much.
It's all about Eiken, isn't it?
It's not about Eiken at all.
In my third year of work, I got a haircut.
Please cut your hair. Give yourself a makeover.
I laughed the most when I owned a store.
Usually when you're a new member of society.
Like, you're going to be the president.
Even the president would have been impressed.
I think I flew off the handle when I got the restaurant too soon.
When you've been around 120 times, you just fly off the handle.
Owning a restaurant is like making your own territory within the company.
You have to create your own territory within the company and do it in a place where you can ask questions freely.
I can work in a place where I can ask questions freely.
I can work without stress.
You are a great professional.
That's what I was thinking about.
Not a side job.
It says to get out of it quickly.
But it's easy for a variety of people to come in and give advice.
It's easy to plan as a variety.
It was great.
It was my first time in a showroom.
I'm glad it was the Juno Emmer Kai. First-time visitor.
Thank you very much.
Please take a look next time.
Please take a look.
Yes, I will. Then, please close.
Mr. Emmer.
You are the MC, right?
He closes the show every time.
I'd like to see Emmer's closing.
What? You're closing?
It's like I've done many weeks of my life.
I've done 120 weeks.I've done 120 weeks.
I think there is a good way to close.
I'll close it then.
Se-no! Pon!
Is that what I think it is?
Bye-bye!
Okay, at this point
The time for the video is